<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidTraining</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="action_message">Edit message</string>
    <string name="action_display">Display</string>
    <string name="action_add">Add</string>
    <string name="dropdown">DropDown</string>
    <string name="tabs">Tabs</string>
    <string name="menu_login">Login</string>

    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="edit_firstname">Enter first name</string>
    <string name="edit_lastname">Enter last name</string>
    <string name="edit_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="edit_password_repeat">Re-enter password</string>
    <string name="hint_last_signed_user">Last signed user</string>

    <string name="button_send">Send</string>
    <string name="button_dogs">Dogs</string>
    <string name="button_rafa">Rafa</string>
    <string name="button_android">Android</string>
    <string name="button_save">Save String to IM</string>
    <string name="button_load">Load String from IM</string>
    <string name="button_signin">Sign in</string>
    <string name="button_intents">Try Intents !</string>
    <string name="button_phone">Phone Intent</string>
    <string name="button_map">Map Intent</string>
    <string name="button_web">Web Intent</string>
    <string name="button_mail">Mail Intent</string>
    <string name="button_calendar">Calendar Intent</string>
    <string name="button_contact">Contact Intent</string>
    <string name="button_implicit">Implicit Intent</string>
    <string name="button_alarm">Alarm Intent</string>
    <string name="button_timer">Timer Intent</string>
    <string name="button_camera">Camera Intent</string>
    <string name="button_camera_still">Still Cam Intent</string>
    <string name="button_video">Video Intent</string>
    <string name="button_file_retrieve">Retrieve File Intent</string>
    <string name="button_file_open">Open File Intent</string>
    <string name="button_taxi">Taxi Intent</string>
    <string name="button_music">Music Intent</string>
    <string name="button_music_search">Music Search Intent</string>
    <string name="button_web_search">Web Search Intent</string>
    <string name="button_settings">Settings Intent</string>
    <string name="button_mms">MMS Intent</string>
    <string name="button_intent_service">Intent Service</string>
    <string name="button_service">Service</string>
    <string name="button_bind_service">Bind Service</string>
    <string name="button_request_file">Request File</string>
    <string name="chooser_title">Share this message via</string>
    <string name="button_database_title">Database</string>
    <string name="button_media_title">Media</string>
    <string name="button_media_raw">Raw Resource</string>
    <string name="button_media_uri">URI Resource</string>
    <string name="button_media_url">URL Resource</string>
    <string name="button_release">Release !</string>
    <string name="button_media_service">Media Service</string>
    <string name="button_release_service">Destroy service</string>
    <string name="button_media_foreground_service">Media Foreground</string>
    <string name="button_media_stop_foreground">Stop Foreground</string>
    <string name="button_record">Record This !</string>
    <string name="button_camera_app">Camera App</string>
    <string name="button_capture">Capture</string>
    <string name="button_video_capture">Video App</string>
    <string name="button_print_image">Print Image</string>
    <string name="button_print_document">Print Document</string>


    <string name="title_activity_display_message">My Message</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display">Images</string>
    <string name="title_saved_string">Saved String:</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <!-- String aliasing => hi_world = hello_world reference -->
    <string name="hi_world">@string/hello_world</string>
    <string name="count">Count</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="activity_monitor">Activity Monitor</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_drop_down_navigation">DropDownNavigationActivity</string>

    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="count_value_key">count</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="title_activity_intents">IntentsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_file_select">FileSelectActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_database">DatabaseActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_media">MediaActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_record">RecordActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_camera">CameraActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_video">VideoActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bitmap">BitmapActivity</string>

    <string name="button_load_raw">Load Raw</string>
    <string name="button_load_bitmap">Load Bitmap</string>
    <string name="textView_load_time">Load time</string>
    <string name="button_load_efficiently">Load Efficiently</string>
    <string name="radio_100_100">100x100</string>
    <string name="radio_400_400">400x400</string>
    <string name="radio_800_800">800x800</string>
    <string name="radio_1600_1600">1.6x1.6</string>
    <string name="button_load_asynchronously">AsyncTask</string>
    <string name="button_concurrency">Concurrency</string>
    <string name="button_cache_load">Cache</string>
    <string name="button_viewpager">ViewPager</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_pager">ViewPagerActivity</string>
    <string name="imageView_viewPager_test">ViewPager test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_grid">GridActivity</string>
    <string name="button_grid_view">GridView</string>
    <string name="title_activity_open_gl">OpenGLActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_animation">AnimationActivity</string>
    <string name="button_animation">Animation</string>
    <string name="textView_title">Title</string>
    <string name="textView1_sceneA">Text Line 1</string>
    <string name="textView2_sceneA">Text Line 2</string>
    <string name="button_start_animation">Animate</string>
    <string name="button_add_items">Add Items</string>
    <string name="button_remove_me">Move Me !</string>
    <string name="textView_steve">Steven Paul Steve Jobs February 24, 1955 – October 5, 2011 was an American pioneer of the personal computer revolution of the 1970s (along with engineer, inventor, and Apple Computer co-founder, Steve Wozniak). Shortly after his death, Jobss official biographer, Walter Isaacson described him as the creative entrepreneur whose passion for perfection and ferocious drive revolutionized six industries: personal computers, animated movies, music, phones, tablet computing, and digital publishing.[2]

Adopted at birth in San Francisco and raised in the San Francisco Bay Area during the 1960s, Jobss countercultural lifestyle was a product of his time. As a senior at Homestead High School, in Cupertino, California, his two closest friends were the older engineering student (and Homestead High alumnus) Steve Wozniak and his countercultural girlfriend, the artistically inclined Homestead High junior Chrisann Brennan. Jobs briefly attended Reed College in 1972 before dropping out, deciding to travel through India in 1974, and study Buddhism.

In addition, Jobss proximity to Silicon Valley influenced his interest in the budding personal computer industry of the 1970s. After a brief period at Atari, Inc., he co-founded Apple in 1976 in his parents Los Altos home on Crist Drive in order to sell Wozniaks Apple I personal computer. Jobs and Woz gained fame and wealth a year later for the Apple II (which was designed primarily by Wozniak, but Jobs oversaw the development of its unusual case and Rod Holt developed the unique power supply) one of the first highly successful mass-produced personal computers. The Apple II dominated the personal computer market until it was destabilized by the introduction of the IBM-PC (powered by Microsofts MS-DOS) in 1981.

In 1979, after a tour of Xerox PARC, Jobs saw the commercial potential of the Xerox Alto (which was mouse-driven and had a graphical user interface or GUI). After failing to create such a device with the Apple Lisa (which Jobs named after his daughter with Chrisann, Lisa, a fact that Jobs would only admit years later after he initially denied paternity), he turned to the struggling Macintosh team. In January 1984, Jobs launched the original Macintosh (the first mass-produced computer with a graphical user interface) with the 1984 commercial broadcast during the Super Bowl. The Macintosh also instigated the sudden rise of the desktop publishing industry in 1985 with the addition of the Apple LaserWriter, the first laser printer to feature vector graphics.

Despite the fanfare, the expensive Macintosh was a hard sell.[3] Shortly after its release in 1985, Bill Gates then-developing company, Microsoft, threatened to stop developing Mac applications unless it was granted a license for the Mac operating system software. Microsoft was developing its graphical user interface ... for DOS, which it was calling Windows and didnt want Apple to sue over the similarities between the Windows GUI and the Mac interface.[4] Sculley granted Microsoft the license which later led to problems for Apple.[4] In addition, cheap IBM PC clones that ran on Microsoft software and had a graphical user interface began to appear. Although the Macintosh preceded the clones, it was far more expensive, so through the late 80s, the Windows user interface was getting better and better and was thus taking increasingly more share from Apple.[5] Windows based IBM-PC clones also led to the development of additional GUIs such as IBMs TopView or Digital Researchs GEM,[5] and thus the graphical user interface was beginning to be taken for granted, undermining the most apparent advantage of the Mac...it seemed clear as the 80s wound down that Apple couldnt go it alone indefinately against the whole IBM-clone market.[5]

Jobs continued to promote the Macintosh undeterred by its prohibitive cost, much to the ire of Apples board. After a long power struggle, Jobs was forced out of the company in September in 1985.[6] He then underwent a number of changes during the period of 1985-1996. After leaving Apple, he subsequently took a few of its members with him to found NeXT, a computer platform development company specializing in state of the art, higher end computers for higher-education and business markets. A few years later in 1990, Tim Berners-Lee would use a NeXT Computer to create the first browser for the World Wide Web. In addition to NeXT, Jobs helped to instigate the development of the visual effects industry when he funded the spinout of the computer graphics division of George Lucas company Lucasfilm in February 1986.[7] The new company, renamed Pixar, would eventually produce the first fully computer-generated animated film, Toy Story, an event made possible in part due to Jobss financial support.

Jobs also focused on his family during this time period. After the death of his adoptive mother from cancer in 1986, he found his birth mother and discovered that his biological sister is the author Mona Simpson. He also fully acknowledged paternity for Lisa, and had her name legally changed to Lisa Brennan-Jobs. Finally, in 1991, Jobs married Stanford Business School graduate, Laurene Powell in a Buddhist ceremony and had three more children with her.

By 1997, Apple was nearly bankrupt. Jobs thus negotiated Apples purchase of NeXT (the NeXTSTEP platform would become the foundation for Mac OS X) which would allow him to return as the companys interim CEO. He would eventually became Apples CEO and bring the company back to profitability by 1998. Beginning in 1997 with the Think different campaign, Jobs began to work closely with designer Jonathan Jony Ive towards a line of devices (named by ad executive Ken Segall) that would have larger cultural ramifications: the iMac (1998); iTunes, the Apple Stores, and the iPod (2001); the iTunes Store (2003); the iPhone (2007); the App Store (2008); and the iPad (2010).

Jobs was diagnosed with a pancreas neuroendocrine tumor in 2003 and died of respiratory arrest related to the tumor on October 5, 2011.</string>
    <string name="button_cross_fade">Cross Fade</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_pager_animation">ViewPagerAnimationActivity</string>
    <string name="button_zoomout">Zoom Out</string>
    <string name="button_depthpage">Depth Page</string>
    <string name="steve_jobs_close_up">Close up image of Steve Jobs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_card_flip">CardFlipActivity</string>
    <string name="button_flipcard">FlipCard</string>
    <string name="menu_show_info">Show info</string>
    <string name="menu_show_image">Show Image</string>
    <string name="button_zoom_animation">Zoom Animation</string>
    <string name="title_activity_zoom_animation">ZoomAnimationActivity</string>
    <string name="rafa_thumbnail_description">Rafa thumbnail</string>
    <string name="rafa_image_full_size_description">Rafa image in full size</string>
    <string name="prairie_dogs_image_description">Prairie thumbnail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_items">AddItemsActivity</string>
    <string name="button_add">Add</string>

</resources>
